oh marketing is is another name for
hacking I mean instead of hacking I mean
it really hacking really computers
marketing relates to people right you're
hacking people yeah um yeah go watch go
watch social
[Music]
dilemma
all right sup
guys I have been working my butt off on
this live hacking event so it's great to
take a break and talk to you guys about
this week's podcast episode that I'm
super excited for because we brought on
the show John coulston AKA
mayonnaise John is someone you will see
often at the top of the leaderboards on
hacker one because he takes a data
science approach to bug Bounty and that
really helps him multiply his findings
every every finding that he has he's
able to sort of narrow down what kind of
vulnerabilities and problems that these
companies are having and apply those to
other endpoints to find more bugs so
it's a really fascinating interview I
hope you'll enjoy it I most certainly
did in addition to that we've also got
the uh word fence bug Bounty program
running a 6.25 times promotion again if
you haven't already signed up for this
platform you're crazy you've signed up
for hacker one you've signed up for bug
crowd you've signed up for integrity why
haven't you signed up for word fence yet
so head over to ctbb show/ WF sign up
for a researcher account today so you
can stay in the loop and hear about
these awesome promotions every time they
come up I've been uh I've been working
on that program a little bit and I've
got some Automation in place that is
producing a good number of bugs at a set
pace so um for any of you that like
static code analysis there's definitely
an opportunity there to get some
Automation in place as well all righty
with that let's go ahead and jump to the
episode with
John Al righty John I am looking at this
massive document over here to the right
right now filled with like pretty much
just gold on the the crossover between
data science and Bug Bounty thanks so
much for coming to the show man and
thanks so much for all the effort you
put into prepping for it thanks J for
having me yeah um for those that don't
know who I am my name is John coulston I
go by the uh handle of minis or my own
eyes or Mayo I go through all three of
those um and I got into um into the bug
Bounty World about five years ago and
I've been working at it to various level
since
then so so dude yeah mayonnaise I I've
always thought about this mayonnaise is
like pretty odd name give us like the
the 30 second Summary of why you chose
that name and and uh and it definitely
made you a figure in the in the bug
Bounty face we like who's this guy
calling himself mayonnaise yes so um
it's funny I young John was a huge fan
of the Smashing Pumpkins and the SES
dream album uh was one of those Life
Changers right and there's a song on
there and everybody called it mayonnaise
but it's it's spelled man with one in uh
and then somewhere along the years I
researched the meaning of it and it's
actually like a phonetic play it's my
own eyes instead of manise the drop of
the my own eyes my own eyes and so I
thought weird pronunciation yeah so I
said that's perfect you know for a hack
of my own eyes SE the stuff and uh and
it related to something you know that uh
I enjoy which is music and that's how
that came
together that's awesome man there's so
many different areas so let me let me
back up a little bit the reason why we
wanted to bring you on the Pod is uh
time and time again on the critical
thinking podcast here we have discussed
the part of
hacking relating to data and to taking
notes on a specific Target right and so
many of the people that we have on are
just like yeah you know I take notes in
this a.txt file and it's really like
rough and there's no system to it it's
it's just kind of like I write things
down on this paper and I stick it in my
shoe or something like that right it's
it's all over the place and we're like I
was thinking okay we've got so many um
takes on that perspective let me get a
different perspective and I was thinking
who is the most organized and who is the
most methodical you know data driven
hacker that I know and you came to mind
so what I'm hoping to get out of today
um is is a little bit of a look into how
you use data science to win bug bounties
and man if you look at your hacker one
profile you're you're winning it man
it's great um and and so I want to know
about how you've done that and um I know
also that you have a uh specific
propensity for digital marking Marketing
in your past experiences and kind of how
that plays into the data science into
the hacking role um and to get that
holistic perspective I think we're going
to have to go back a little bit and hear
about um your your career path and your
career history and how you kind of got
into this digital marketing and data
science areas um that made you the
hacker you are today so give us a little
brief introduction to that if you would
yeah so um so I went to uh Georgia Tech
and you know I graduated um in 1999
which was the kind of the height of the
do boom right my focus was in
information
technology and and went went to work for
a startup um and um was integrated as a
as a consultant into a credit card
company was responsible building out a
lot of their information systems um and
integrating the technology that we built
was a realtime decision engine um to be
able to approve customers for credit
card Real Time online that was like new
stuff wow that's a big deal yeah and uh
so yeah went through that um eventually
started working for the credit company
um did a new Venture I guess underneath
there that we eventually got acquired
because the whole V Generation Um
vertical was exploding so got um into
that um I guess in that industry as part
of an acquisition built out several
National Brands um and with that you
know you had not television you know
radio but you had an incredible amount
of digital media or digital advertising
that would go on and so I was
responsible as all the analytics to tie
everything together make sure that every
dollar spent was accountable generating
return and um worked very closely
especially with the digital man uh
digital marketing team to be able to
understand okay what levers are being
pushed how do I now provide them with
the information to help them make the
decisions needed to to um you know
perform better and and and acquire
customers at a lower cost and at a
higher
volume so that's kind of how I got into
the whole that now uh as far as like you
how that transitioned to um to bug
Bounty I eventually had gone on to start
doing my own
um uh a business that was in a
completely different vertical still
Legion um but it was in the mortgage
space uh we hit some walls at one point
with compliance trying to get through um
some legal matters and um I needed to
figure out some how to earn some income
while we work through those issues and
uh you know found a freelance
opportunity and and hacking it was
something that I was aware of it was on
my radar which was so busit doing this
anyway so I jumped in and um having a
background in in you know data science
and and uh analytics and whatnot I took
that approach I took a very methodical
data processing how do I approach this
type of uh
mentality um and then stuck hard to one
program and I believe that was probably
a little bit of naivity about how the
bug b space was back then you know
favoring loyalty but um yeah that's kind
of how I went into
the dude that's that's such an
interesting start because one of the
advice pieces of advice that I give to
most people that are trying to start bug
Bounty is like hey you can't really be
in a situation where you're uh you know
trying to enter the industry to make
money because you're in some sort of you
know situation where you you don't have
your your finances squared down and uh
not only did you know and and you know
maybe not speaking to the finan part but
you were transitioning out of a out of a
you know a situation with your startup
where you needed to find some additional
income and going into the space which
adds additional pressures and then you
know coming from a a non-security
related field and just taking that
expertise from that field and applying
it to bug Bounty um I'm not going to lie
man I would have bet against you I would
have bet against you that that that you
wouldn't have been able to pull it off
as well as you did but you did that's
amazing so so I mean you know working
with data with everything right uh and
as I was reading up right A lot of it
had to do about hacking apis well okay
I'm very familiar with apis that was not
something that so then I was like okay
how do how do you find apis right and
then so you go through that process and
then as you're reading and and so much
content was out there it was basically
saying you know get you know get access
to systems and you go through well
quickly I realized whenever I got on to
the yahu is that okay one they're in
clean up clean up mode right they're one
of the original advertising platforms if
not the original original advertising
platforms that were out there so the
technology was going to be
old doubling that up over right is that
okay they're spending their time on the
P public facing assets right so you
knew if you can get into the business of
business the B2B type of
applications then you're going to have
um opportunities that were going to be
once in a lifetime right I mean you
going to have yeah dude this is this is
such a intuitive approach man you're
you're like okay let me just think so if
I was going to hack I need to find apis
and how do I find apis well I find some
sketchy advertising company and I like
that you went in your vertical as well
you say that's that's another thing we
talk about a lot on the pot is like if
you can hack within your vertical within
the thing that you understand within the
industry that you're familiar with
whether from a hobby perspective or from
a work perspective that's going to
afford you a tremendous Advantage um and
that's what you did so you went after
you went after Yahoo here anybody who
has ever looked at the Yahoo leaderboard
knows that you went after Yahoo um and
and uh you were finding apis left and
right and you were trying to get your
hands on these these uh business B2B
applications or some of this older stuff
right right exactly and so you know when
you find the apis and this goes back to
the the journal you're talking about
right uh I would find those apis they're
not vulnerable at that point in time but
they they provide a wealth of
information so whenever I do get access
or whatever or it helps me identify hey
there's a system out there that I'm not
aware of I don't know what the login is
but I can start researching that so it
was it was a um a a an effort to be able
to to identify the um the different
platforms that were out there um which
was incredible the number of them Yahoo
had and Al had gone through all these uh
murders and Acquisitions I mean you had
all these other bolt-on um ad platforms
that were out there so it was just it it
was a a a a garden of opportunity yeah
yeah and all of it was you know all says
I say a mess he says a garden a garden
of opportunity that just needed to be uh
harvested so great man I love that I
sign up for that
job yeah no clear clearly clearly and
and so you know you stuck for the
beginning you know you kind of stuck
into your into your vertical there and
you were looking at Yahoo spending a lot
of time on them um I guess and and
nowadays are you still looking at Yahoo
primarily or you have you kind of moved
along how has your methodology evolved
from those Early times to to now
nowadays yeah so um you
know John Coulson mayonnaise 2024 is
completely different than 22 right um
and so back in the day I was I was
fully committed um and spent an insane
amount of time focusing on Yahoo and
knew that the opportunity was limited
and and the boundaries were good and um
so I just
went so deep um and and when I going
deep on applications it wasn't
necessarily going deep into the
technology it was going you know Finding
if there were any seminars and that were
out there or public education you know
B2B type thing what were some of the
things that were being pushed out to the
industry that I could then like okay hey
you know they're they're releasing some
new technology called immersion okay and
I need to figure out what that is where
does that live and things that nature so
I would I'd use that also as a as a lead
um to be able to try to find uh things
on the platform and go from there um and
so about that would you would you
automate that actual part of it yourself
or was this just you kind of being
plugged into the data sources for Yahoo
and like what's happening with the
platform and that sort of thing both so
the I mean the automation was it was
constant so constantly going after and
finding what are the new assets that
were coming out um looking at the uh the
domain names and say hey this is the
word I'm not familiar with is that new
product so you know do I need to search
this more and and it would Dov tell them
a lot of manual um searching and looking
for you know documentations that you
know a development team would use to
integrate their system into their you
know into the ad system because they've
got a bunch of stuff to do to be able to
determine you know my budgets and where
I'm going to put placement and things
that just they there these companies are
tied into multiple platforms and there's
Integrations that go on so there's
documentation flying around on that kind
of stuff as well right right um so yeah
and all that kind of
uh all those things were what I was used
to be able to help guide me and identify
those SP so there was I mean I know how
many platforms I was able to get to and
put my hands on um but yeah that was
that was my that was my goal dud the the
layer the the depth there right I just
want to point out you know the fact that
you said hey there's a I'm monitoring
subdomains right which is you know
something that's fairly normal in the
bugb industry it's something we do and
then he says and there was a word I
didn't re I didn't know
like like this is this is the level of
granularity that I feel like a lot of
people don't realize that you need in
bug Bounty because you know when you
look at the list of you know 20,000
subdomains or more that you get back
from you know uh running a a subdomain
enumeration scan on Yahoo uh it can be
overwhelming but then John says hey
there's actually a new subdomain that
just popped up with a word that I don't
know in it let me go and research what's
happening with this company let me try
to figure out what transitions are
happening at this current time with the
company and dive deep into that so
that's that's amazing man so it can
expose it expose a new product a new
platform a new technology um so yeah
understanding what you know what the do
domain names provide you uh gives you a
a of what's going on behind the scenes
so so there's the new stuff that's
happening the new transitions that are
happening with the company there's the
old old old stuff that you're getting
access to you know these Antiquated
applications um you've said in the notes
here you know somewhere that it was like
stuff that that was sort of pre-security
life cycle like security wasn't even a
thought really at the time when some of
these applications were being developed
because it was so you know long ago um
and so getting access to those core
applications is important but that's
tricky right getting access to uh some
of these more complex um more uh Niche
uh platforms so I mean how were you
mostly hacking from an unauthenticated
perspective did you how how did you get
your hands on credentials or how did you
actually hack these platforms
so yeah so um ultimately you had to get
well 90% of the time you had to get
credentials right um so a lot of the a
lot of the automation hacking would
build a a portfolio of documents that
you would then Silo into okay this is
probably AOL one or this is you know DSP
or something right right so you had the
weth of the documentation not don't and
then you'd find um so you you know the
the typical way that you you go about U
is okay can I find a place to Brute
Force okay that's limited um but even
with the limitations you know being on
the business side of things this is a
good tip to take back right if you're on
a hacking a B2B system and um you know
that at some point they're going to have
demo accounts or test accounts so that
they can share with other businesses
okay so if you're able to identify in
some capacity that okay it's demo at
blah yahoo.com whatever and it and you
you're people find some screen or you
some user dump I don't know but you see
that okay that that user is meant to be
shared and
therefore that password is probably
going to be very simplistic and a
standard um Brute Force password cracker
will go after
right so that's one way um another way
um especially on the BWB is that if you
can figure out who are the users like
which businesses have used the pl
platform and you're able to uh assemble
that and
monitor which of those companies go out
of
business and then buy their domain buy
their domain and
then the N approach so there was a
fortunate you know I was able to to
download a list and then I memorized
every user in that list and all the
domains you can't save it that's great
so I memorized all of them right and uh
know and then you know I Monitor and see
okay is that GoDaddy has a great tool
for that this this domain available oh
it is okay let me register that domain
and create an email address I and now
let me try to do some let me do a pass
reset so now two Factor authentication
is kind of taken over that right and and
and if even if you get even if you get
if you brute force an account or you um
do some typ account take over there I'm
tell you're nine times out of 10 you're
going to get a hard stop from the from
the company y okay great the bug ends
there um I do recommend saying hey uh
once I get in I didn't poke around much
but I like to see what I can do over the
next X hours would that be possible you
might get a reprieve um and and you know
permission to go in uh but ultimately I
think that that if you can figure out a
way to overcome whatever barriers it is
to get an account in your own
credentials then they can't stop you
they can't stop you so yeah I would
highly
recommend so so you can also you know
know so that's ways that we can sort of
compromise accounts with with um you
know trying to Brute Force some stuff or
or getting be able to do password resets
on people whose domains have expired um
and then getting your own account that's
a whole different Beast right because
like you you have to in those scenarios
you kind of gota you kind of be able got
to be able to walk the walk and talk the
talk to say like hey yeah I know about
this product yeah I'm interested in
using this product for my business that
sort of thing and getting that all set
up have you have you had experience with
that uh yeah so
um have tried many different times
failed quite a bit whenever you you know
trying to tend to be a business um I
think the my favorite story to tell is
um is obtaining access to the Taiwan
assets of Yahoo um because those assets
required um a physical presence within
the country and a phone number um and so
and maybe even an additional ID but
there was a there was a huge barrier
unless you were in Tai uh you were very
limited so I um through several attempts
the first three or four failed but
finally figured out the the winning
methodology is that I posted a job on
upwork um and I was looking for an
English
translator and and and it was you you
had to be where I felt is that I was
like try to hire them on and then I'm
telling them what I would do and they
were like no I'm not going to hack no
they would go away so in the job posting
I said lifetime opportunity ride shotgun
with a hacker is we blah blah blah blah
and go after and dude yeah the response
board just lit up like it was like
immediately slow slow down and so um I
was able to find uh this wonderful lady
named Lexi in uh Taiwan she uh she had a
family member that actually had uh the
you know uh the mall and store and all
that to had those accounts she she was
you know enough familiar so we're like
all right let's go and we registered and
it was like you know yeah we went
through the whole process and registered
and uh she was in my eyes and ears and
and got me in and yeah no it was uh
right timing for a for live hacking
event it was just it was everything was
great um that's amazing so so this you
know you went through those you jumped
through those hoops and then you've got
yourself an account and now you've got
access to the scope that nobody has
access to ex exactly exactly and you've
got creds and you've got all these old
apis and you know beginning of the
marketing era tools that you've got them
all to yourself wow yeah
that always for M like I mean my skill
as a as a hacker
is is secondary right um compared to
like when I
watch when you guys talk about oh yeah
we inserted a hyperlink with this tag
and then we redirected
and then we somehow got a heat dump in
which we had the creds for the entire
company on AWS I mean okay fantastic I'm
not going to go there that's my skill
set but if I can get to assets that you
know that or that are in uh in line more
my skill set then I'm going to that's
what I'm doing so that was that's how I
went after
things uh that's great man and and this
whole this whole concept of of going
deeper and deeper and deeper than people
people think you should go or people
think you you uh have to go to find
these various assets and get access to
these systems and understand the company
at a deeper level that's one of the core
core things that's really important in
bug Bounty and you've kind of nailed it
um so we we've talked a good bit bit
about that um I want to swing back
around to the so we're going to go two
places here we're going to go the data
we want to talk about data science and
how you use data science to you know uh
more specifically granularly how you're
using that in your recon flow how you're
using it to predict vulnerabilities and
that sort of thing and then I also want
to talk about specific because clearly
you have a lot of Industry expertise on
digital marketing I want to talk about
digital marketing Platforms in
particular in some sort of um I guess
you know hands on the keyboard or you
know looking at the data uh tips and
tricks for um how to do that so let's
let's start with let's start with data
science um obviously for me let me just
kind of give a little brain dump of what
I'm thinking here so when I think data
science plus bug Bounty I'm thinking
mostly from a Recon perspective but if
you look at your hacker one profile
you're not just doing recon you're
finding a lot of VES so I'm wondering
how how much of your methodology with
that uses data science is is pertaining
to reconnaissance and how much of it
actually gives you a a tangible
vulnerability and um and then I guess
you can kind of talk about either one of
those Recon and and the actual uh
vulnerability
itself yes so
um figuring out how to best approach
this and and um explain it so data
science
um I use it as a construct it's not a
one and done type thing applying it to
to word list it's it's applying it to
right right uh everything I do and so to
do that
um I go under the Matra Peter duer he's
a he's a management um philosopher he he
came up with this saying is what is not
measured is not managed right and so
when you when you put everything into
that
framework is is that you want to measure
everything and because if you if you're
able to measure it then you're able to
optimize it so um to to do that in you
know bug Bounty most of us whenever I
watch hackers use the tools they're a
oneandone right it's not built into some
system that's intended to keep track of
performance that you can then later go
back at a future date and make
modifications and and do your
optimization so I built a system that
like whenever I run a fuzz on a Target
right it's going to log everything that
I do so I have wrappers around all my
tools and I call I call that that that
worker with this and I make sure that
all that information goes
into uh I say a database but flat files
that I can later use
okay I'm gonna pause you right there
because there's just so much to unwind
just right there okay so first first
step first step is we need to measure
everything so that we can optimize
everything so that we can perform better
as bani hunters in order to do that what
you've done is you've wrapped all of
your tools with some sort of um I I
guess some sort of script or something
that is going to be taking the output of
that tool and allowing you to retrieve
the output later if you need to or can
you just talk a little bit it's going
into flat files you know you say a
database but it's going into flat files
and then you're SE ing those flat files
for patterns that you've identified is
that the idea so okay so yeah next next
level so let's just
take we have one file that we're fuzzing
right it's a generic file and you're
fuzzing it on all domains right so let's
take a look at all the ways that we can
measure that right so we have a domain
right we know what the program is we
know the subdomain of that program or
whatever the root is right those are two
pieces of traceability that you need to
have right so you not only domain
subdomain and and program right then um
you give it the file how big is that
file what is the purpose that file and
can I track it so I know the identity of
it right so how many records in right
how many records out how many successful
hits did it have and your definition of
successful hit could be different
between people whatever right so now I
have a hit rate for that file by that
program by that
route okay so now I can start seeing
okay this particular file is going to
have a performance of X on here so now
whenever you start looking at the bigger
picture of things I have a hit rate of X
percent here and Y percent here why is
that right okay this this then you start
getting to the topics of relevancy and
and all that stuff right so that's a
very gener you're correlating uh I can
see I I'm starting to see it here so so
you know you say okay I ran this across
this specific set of subdomains I'd
expect I get this specific hit rate I
run it across this subdomains and wow
this hit rate is specifically you know
drastically different what what is am I
doing something wrong here is does this
file just not exist on these subdomains
um but they they're they should exist so
maybe a certain you know uh path is
mapped wrong or or incorrectly or
differently or something like that and
wow okay interesting so applying it to
Flat files you're not going to have that
much of a difference but whenever you
start whenever you start getting into
your like specific files that okay so
all my files have a unique purpose like
I have a purpose this file is meant to
find apis this file is meant to find
endpoints that reveal directory
structures or additional endpoints
within the
server this file is meant for find
upload features I I don't you you have
right you'll quickly be able to start
finding things accordingly by program
You by you know the actual route within
the program and be able to see what
you're doing well and what you're doing
not right if you can identify okay here
are my top performers here's my 10 top
performers why why why is it performing
well what is happening
here that I can then so where I'm going
is that whenever you take a look and you
just look at your standard
your output of how do you how do you
measure it how how do you know you're
improving on your fuzzing how do you
know that your word list is applicable
or relevant to this file or to this
program or this program or this program
so now now once you build a and this is
a bit of an Overkill I I and only reason
why I do this is
because hey you said you said it not me
man I no it's an Overkill and and and
and and and what I only hope is that you
know for people for the the audience
that's listening here is that you can
take a little tidbit so in you don't
have to build out this Mass system but
but being able to understand um you know
how to put together a construct so you
can start measuring performance across
you different programs different bird
lists different sections so how's your
crawler doing you know how's your link
finder doing you know why is it clearly
I'm missing out on some keyword for this
program because its hit rate is very low
what's unique about it let me try to
spend some extra time fuzzing on it to
see if there's okay there's a different
path to you know the files that I
normally use to be able to determine
like a directory
structure so it kind of identifies areas
where you can focus and then
whatnot so you're you're assigning
performance you're measuring even down
to like the the path in the directory
level and creating lists and analytics
that are are telling you about the
efficiency of specific like directory
brute forcing list
entries that granularly yeah and and
where where it goes in is okay so wow so
I have so I have um so as I have
workflows right and so my one of my main
workflows goes through a a series and it
looks something like this it's like a
quick hit fuzz of like
things that's going to reveal directory
structure on right and some of API but a
lot of us like robot Texs asset manifest
things of that nature right sure okay
goes in run a
crawler uh run a link finder okay now
you know words are you know that are
relevant to the host are are generated
okay put those words into a you know
recipe ingredient type mix run that
through do I get additional hits okay so
I'm stepping through through a series of
I don't know 30 different subprocesses
within this
workflow and I need to be able to manage
it I need to have kpis on each one how
you know so all the way back to okay
it's part of this program came from this
subdomain that is the that this is the
actual subdomain but this was a root
domain okay it goes through all right
here are the performance of the TW 30
steps of this process is the results
okay now now I can aggregate that up I
can now say okay this program or this
route or you know with the performances
of the hit rates and whatnot that's just
in like content
Discovery you go back and you start
doing know a diff you know different
analysis from a standpoint of oh um you
know did I get a bug right and then
trace it back so as soon as I get a bug
I'm going back I'm going back tracing
through all the processes all the way
back to how did I find that what was
what was the source like was this part
of a uh a pull from security Trails was
it like a cidr scin what what it was
right and so yeah yeah yeah by putting
all this together you start
understanding now this is very it falls
into the automation realm I heard that
being kicked around and right yeah yeah
for sure 100% right and so there's tools
that can like this concept can be
applied to people that not necessarily
are wanting to build Out full aist you
can build out you can use this concept
to build out okay I'm going to do a new
keyword Discovery tool right because I
need to add and grow my word L okay well
let's use that I I want I want to hear
about I want to hear about that and and
I want to also go back to what you were
saying before about tracing the
vulnerability now you found the
vulnerability let me see what parts of
my process led to me finding that
endpoint which found to that
vulnerability but first I want to get a
little bit into the the Weeds on how
exactly you're doing this because I was
like when I hear you talk about um
statistical analysis on paths and and
stuff like that I'm like wow that sounds
really cool I should have all of my word
list sorted by hey this is the ones that
are going to hit first you know uh
statistically across you know a big set
of data um but but I'm a little bit like
when I start thinking about how I'm
going to program that and how I'm going
to do that it gets a little bit it gets
a little bit fuzzy for me so I mean
obviously how are you you said you
mentioned flat file
you said database and then you're like
well it's actually flat files I mean are
you are you Computing efficiency for
these specific um paths and then like
storing them in a flash F in a flat fly
in like CSV format and then like dumping
it in after you've sorted it with I
don't know how are you doing this yeah
yeah yeah it's not quite as automated as
what you're going it's just I'm
collecting the data that leads me to the
information or leads me to where I can
start diving so let's
say this process it has X number of
subprocesses right I'm going to like I I
know what each subprocess does so I know
the word list that it uses but I'm going
to count in like how many in how many
records in how many hits right and I'm
GNA dump that to a kpi log right so for
this a process this is the in this out
and this is the time duration
because okay
whenever yeah where I'm going with this
is that I want at theend at the end of
the day I want to sit down have a cup of
coffee spend two hours writing reports
and then and then go play off I that's
what I want to but
that's that's that's the end goal I'm
not trying to be like I'm not trying to
be the guy I'm not trying to be like
iate this great attack vector and like I
am what I am I call this practice
retirement right now I I'm figuring out
what I to do but
I I'm you know I'm uh I'm living the
good life I'm taking my intensity down a
bit and if I can have these systems
generate a list of what I call
opportunities I'm
basically I'm bu I'm building a lead
generation platform for hackers it's
going to give me leads at the end of the
day there's going to be opportunities
and that's a great way to call it right
there it's lead gen for V yeah exactly
exactly what I'm trying to build I'm not
I'm not doing it's not vulnerability
scanning well that is part of it you
know you can run nucle nuclei all day
long uh and find and find stff there but
this is this is stuff that is tailored
just to me right and so let's say let's
say there's another hacker that
eventually partner up with that is like
oh I'm like aame is SQL injection okay
what are your flags let me program it in
here's your feed right and so that's
kind of where I'm going with it so wow
that so so okay so but your your your
key your key performance indicators
there
is is um you know your inputs uh you
know you're saying okay I'm fuzzing this
file you know this file of um uh you
know let's say you said you mentioned
quick hits before right we've got like
quick hits. txt or whatever and um we
fuzz that on a Target and then we say
okay uh it took this much time uh
there's this many hits and uh this many
you know uh yeah I guess this many
entries in the thing so you can say okay
you know my percent my success rate on
this specific word list is x%
uh and then but but you're probably not
breaking it down further than that and
saying okay let me take the 6% that hit
no okay because that's just a little bit
crazy because then at that point you'd
have to actually have a database yeah
well eventually you do from a standpoint
of okay you know what was in contained
in the file you know what your hits were
you know what like so you could filter
down say okay just give me just the hits
that have happened and put it in right
it's more of making sure that you're not
going completely out of rounds okay did
that file run in 20 seconds okay I'm I'm
fine because it's just the initial stage
I don't want it to be um I don't want it
to be be a hog but as you go through my
process I'm bolting on and adding new
stuff and I'm building word list on the
Fly dynamically based upon what's been
um so what words are in the domain okay
those need to be fuzzed need to be
fuzzed in a certain pattern and what you
know words you know xnl link finder find
out that they say hey these are relevant
to the Target okay those need to put in
some type of um recipe ingredient
combination that can then go into be5
right so you
know let's say you're going through and
you see an outlier and all of a sudden
that okay there you found this one step
of your process where you know all of a
sudden there were five million keywords
that were like whoa wait what happened
here right now you're able to go in an
OP that from an optimization standpoint
say okay what specifically occurred here
because that's messed up I don't ever
want that to happen
um or you can or you can say hey this
this particular key you know recipe of
my
keyword um is working really well okay
how can I find other variants of that
that I can then add in so oh is it it's
V2 word internal I don't know what it
okay well now let's let's uh let's go in
and find the three four five one that's
so that's so data driven I love that
because it's like one of the things that
I often do is I I I'll I'll get excited
about that and I'll get all the data and
I'll get it in a database and I'll be
like all right I got all the data you
know and and then I won't even
necessarily go back and be like okay
well what what paths really have been
performing well across this whole you
know this whole Target and what can I
extrapolate from that it's all about
extrapolation in these sort of contexts
too it's like looking at your the things
that you've done that have succeeded and
saying hey why did these succeed and how
can I how can I replicate that um and
and actually I I I mentioned you know a
couple times on the Pod before that I
was really into Recon back in the day
and um I I implemented uh something
similar to this uh where I would you
know even just parsing the words from
the the domain name not nothing else
just the domain name and using those
words to enumerate other domain names
and and this whole concept that we were
talking about uh off air of recipes and
and uh ingredients and that sort of
thing and man I was blown away by the
results man there there's just a ton of
stuff you you'll you'll miss because
it's not in security Trails it's not in
you know any of this other stuff um and
but it is there when you start mixing
you know mixing and matching all these
words together so two questions with
that um one how do you get your
ingredients um you mentioned that you're
using words related to the Target you
know you're pulling it from various
tools um let's say you've got a domain
it's all words just smoosh together how
do you tell where the word starts and
begins okay well so um
one is that
um data science is used for probability
it's not to get 100% so if let's say
there's a domain that is like 36
characters long and there's no dashes
and
dots okay that's a oneof how many other
domains are you ever going to see that
like that again so just stay wash hey
let that one go it's not worth my time
to find that um so yeah so I break down
I break down um the domain
uh subdomains so actually let's start
back we've got all of our different data
repositories that we're pulling from all
that information comes in all right you
have ones that resolve ones that don't
resolve just because they don't resolve
doesn't mean they don't have value make
sure you store something that resolved
in the past you know it could you don't
know it can resolve in the
future so it could resolve on the back
end you know yeah still yes you know you
can still still keep trying to resolve
it over the next 30 days or so whatever
right okay so now you got this
information right um and what you start
looking for is frequency right frequency
of words so you break it down so let's
do um quick example you got I know
10,000 subdomains you break it down by
the dashes and dots and um sometimes you
leave dashes together whatever and then
you do a frequency do a frequency of
what is showing up so you can see API
you can see admin you can see internal
you can see blah blah blah blah right
and what you're going to realize is yeah
so as you go through and so let's say
you take the top you know 100
words right then you say okay what does
this fall into okay this is related to
API okay so this is an API ingredient so
API API 1 yql blah blah blah those are
all you're manually doing this you have
to right I mean there has to be some
type of in the beginning for sure and
yeah I mean so you're grouping and
you'll and you'll find that
um there there's not crazy amounts of
you might get in like the specifics of
you know there might be a particular
company that puts their co-cation in the
BX right um and right right yeah I mean
and
so the Nuance of that and being able to
go through and understand but you you
put together a list of ingredients or
list of each ingredient as you go
through and and the word list will to
tell you what the ingredients are based
on the frequency of what been shown up
in the in the past all right so now
you've got the ingredient so now build a
a loop that says that
replaces those words in your 10,000
domains with the ingredient name right
and then now you start okay res sumarize
that up and then now you start to see
okay and oh and if if there's and if at
the end if there's you haven't um fully
identified all the things just have it
insert a generic word like this word
goes here right so that way you can then
start summarizing up and then say okay
what are my recipes all right so it's
you know
API you know
internal some
word version number word yeah
environment yes BL right and you'll say
oh there's there's my here 20 recipes
that may be specific to that program
maybe very generic for all programs I
mean it depends on what you start with
right wow and and so now
and you see this a lot with with stuff
that with a lot across a lot of
companies and you also see stuff like um
like AWS uh region and and you like you
mentioned you know prod QA that sort of
thing all over the place and yeah these
could be relevant specifically to the
company or these could be across all all
companies it's just a human thing um so
correlating those as well that's that's
great so you've got your ingredients
you've broken those down by the dots and
the dashes um I haven't done any word
splitting uh just mostly done done it
that way and then you've got you've
you've identified and you've grouped
your words so you said okay API words
would be API 1 API 2 a you know that
sort of thing or or like uh maybe it's
like back ending back API you know so
something like that and then you've got
those sort of groups and then you do all
of the combinations of all of them
resolve all of them and then that tells
you I mean obviously you'll definitely
Identify some of the uh additional host
that that you didn't have uh that were
based off of those patterns um but I'm
wondering what other other takeaways as
well you have you have from that where
you can say okay uh this specific word
is particularly High fre frequency or
high performing how can I replicate this
success elsewhere yeah so I I use are
you talking about like using that same
methodology and like content
Discovery do that as well absolutely
there there's definitely there's
definitely that piece and and so you've
got you've got um you've got a list of
ingredients and recipes and you you've
you've enumerated a bunch of subdomains
and now um we're we're going an extra
layer down and so you're using this as
well for Content Discovery yeah yeah
absolutely absolutely so the let talk
about content Discovery right okay so um
let's
say all right so so you're in you're in
your fuzzing stage right and not
mentioned like there's 30 processes in
mind and that this is a number andly how
many they are all right so it goes down
so now we're going to start looking for
words that are relevant because relevant
is a very important aspect of finding
content let's take whatever is relevant
all right so we know that the domain
words are relevant because it provides
information you're going to find threel
acronyms you're going to find products
you're going to find things of that
nature that are list in there all right
so now through your
history if you so now got years worth of
fuzz history that you've now captured
over time right you kind of say okay
what what are what are what are some of
the paths that you commonly see whenever
um a uh you know a a word is listed in
domain how does it how does it apply to
like finding apis right so you take a
look at it you're like okay it I've
noticed now that it takes a word from
the domain all right and I do
domain-i
das Swagger Json or right right right
and so you start adding in and start
playing around with okay how how do I
take the information that I have and
then how do I then apply it extremely
relevant and abbreviated so it's quick I
love this so then there's an extra layer
of this here okay so now now we say okay
what do I know about domains that have
this recipe or what do I know about
domains that have an API Group keyword
in it and then you you can cross
reference because some other host has
some weird you know get all urls uh or
way back you know entry on a different
domain and it's not even the same API
you know string but it's in the same API
Group and so you take you know but
because you're correlating it with the
API Group directly you're grabbing that
string that path and you're trying it on
this totally other host totally
different other host and because you've
drawn the the the connection between
those groups wow dude this is this is
this is crazy so Nel talk
about go the next level and this this is
something I recommend for the Automation
and take to the next level from there
okay all right I'm listening let's go
all right so so there is there is this
need to always look for new keywords
right and grow your list and Val so when
we when we start right we're given a
keyword list that we download from SEC
Ops right or we I'm going to say jhx
because that the key's amazing I'm the
all. text
rate whenever I first started the most
frustrating thing is that there was no
context right every word was of equal
weight when I know that some words are
much more more valuable than others
all right yeah so let's let's take a
let's take a sample where
okay over time we have now if we're
doing a bunch of so let's let's say you
got 10,000 domains but you
know get 10,000 domains some you're
interested in some some you're not
doesn't matter okay still throw them in
there right and take whatever word list
you got and create um some Loop process
bash processes basically say okay I want
you to take the first thousand of that
list and I want you to fuzz least 10,000
dumbing and I want you to dump the
results and then I want you to go back
to the next th and then the next th and
the next th next th and you're just
dumping dumping the results dumping the
results dumping the results right now
now you've got something that provides
you listen what are my hit rates for
each one of those words right now I I
took a list of
2 million right and now I've scrubbed
out and now I've got you know these with
you know a thousand hits and I've got
these with two hits right you now start
to build
weight and then whenever you start
taking a look at weight and then you can
say okay you did that first you know two
million that you got from SE OBS made
you go get a bunch of stuff from asset
it comes in continually feeding this
machine that's just okay DD have I ever
have I ever fuzzed this before yes or no
okay no I haven't okay toss it in and
it's just grinding in the background
just set up a server that does nothing
but this right and then put a reminder
on your calendar so can put in another
you know two million or whatever right
or you're finding like some patterns
whatever and you're like okay let's see
what happens if I do config V2 right and
put and then do every iteration of that
it just sits and runs in the background
on you know and then you just
occasionally go in and it's like oh this
is interesting this is something that
has a high relance rate I need to start
looking into this more and then starting
adding that into so if I can before I
start adding new keywords into my
production files I want to I want to
know that they're relevant right I just
don't want to throw fudge at the wall
and see what sticks do that outside I
want to protect my core processor
and that's great so then we're waiting
we're waiting at that level too and wow
this is this is just you know I knew
that your process here was pretty
in-depth this is a lot deeper than I
than I thought actually so so I'm I'm
very impressed and um there's I'm sure
there's so much more we could dive into
with regards to like where you're
getting all of these these data sources
um and uh you know how how you're
actually going that deep to to you know
correlate all these um but I want I want
to I want to do two things one I want to
um emphasize what you said just a moment
ago which was you went through and you
categorized what words belong to what
conceptual group and I think this is
something that a lot of hackers would
have a little bit of a stigma against
because it's like I'm G to go through
here and I'm G to manually say okay this
belongs to this group this belongs to
this group this belongs to this group
and you it's a manual process especially
automist in general don't love uh you
know manual processes but that's
specific thing that you did requires a
human brain and it requires you to be
able to look at it and say oh this is
you know sort of empathize with the
developer and say that's that's what
they were thinking when they they did
this or this these two ideas are drawn
together by nature of you know how words
work and that sort of thing um and so
using that extra little bit of human
touch I think is a is an extra step that
a lot of people don't go and is really
necessary in the data science world that
that whole
categorization piece right um that's
very cool is there any other scenarios
like that that you could you could um
explain to us and then and then we'll
talk about data sources and where you're
getting um you know like security trails
and that sort of thing as far as like
manual classification um yeah I mean
there's oh I mean it's so built into my
process is I trying to think yeah there
there's so many manual things that I do
right I mean you can't automate
everything you want to be able to look
at at at the stuff um
especially talk to me about your manual
processes then this this will be great
because you know someone who does lean a
lot into automation I want to know what
you do
manually yeah so my manual stuff is now
that I've got a system that collects all
the data I ask questions right and the
manual stuff is investigating like I
know what I'm monitoring but what else
should I be monitoring what else can I
find so if I can if I can spot a uh
Trend um with like um you know some type
of directory structure right that has a
decent headit rate okay let me come up
with a way to create 100,000 variants of
that run it through and see if I get any
hits make it to the production hell and
I might find four bugs while I'm doing
that just in the discovery process right
that's a that's manual um the process is
doing what it's doing but the
concept let's take that example really
quick and say okay walk me through that
so for you what what that looks like is
I'm going to my my and logging into my
server and I'm saying hey what has what
paths have the highest hit
rate yeah so so yeah I mean you can you
can kind of go through that but you know
as you're going through data you'll see
stuff that sticks out like you'll see um
you know you're doing like API all of a
sudden you start seeing with all this
crawl and whatnot you're starting to see
swaggers with variables on it
that's interesting how many other
swaggers do I have with variables do I
have on it right do can I hit it without
the variable I well I can't okay so how
many swaggers am I
missing okay and so it leads you down a
path it's like okay well [__] I need to
figure out what variables I do okay can
I go to Big Data query can I go to asset
no can I find examples of this in any
type of live right what what am I what
are some examples okay it's group one
group two okay that that's that's a
trend okay so let me do you know a bunch
of different tests and and that's going
to go out against all those domains and
see if I can pick up something like
something that I missed or or or pick up
on something that is is being laed out
May maybe it's like oh man here what my
variable value should be part of the you
know the word list that gets dumped out
from XML link finder okay oh what if I
add that in right and or you know
so the manual process is getting in
there getting your hands dirty and
asking the questions and being able to
pull out the data right you don't know
what you don't know and you gota that's
where most of my manual as is it's PR
and for that are you are you are you
mostly like looking at do do you have
are you picking a random host and being
like okay let what is this what
questions can I ask about this host or
you looking at the data from an overall
perspective and saying okay this host
has um you you know a 12% higher hit
rate than other hosts so I'm going to
look at this one or maybe I'm going to
look at the one that doesn't have a very
high hit rate because something's weird
there or how do you how do you how do
you decide yeah so yes so so actually
what what happens so most of this hit
rate stuff for the most part is going to
be more operational make sure I stay
within line I'm not going outside my
target is four minutes five minutes at
Max on a on a if I can get through three
3,000 uh Targets on one server a day
fantastic right that's the dialed into
that right so what happens for me is I
go through all this automation process
blah blah blah blah blah we'll talk
about the conversion funnel but anyway
the output of the conversion funnel at
the very end is a is is a is a log file
for me um that uh that basically has
said what it's discovered the endpoints
it tells me um whether what method was
used get Push Pull blah blah blah it
tells me um or get post pull get post
patch ah okay I see I see I see yes um
what method was used um what stage of
the process it found so if it's a 403 on
a crawl that's going to be more
interesting to me than a 403 on a fuss
because it's much more relevant right so
now I now I have a little information
that okay if I'm going to spend some
time doing four or three bypass I'm
going to do it on the crawl versus you
know so I'm going to wait that
accordingly right and then and then I'm
looking at the end points right look at
all the end points and I'll see
something that I had not expected to see
something that comes out I was like
interesting I have never seen this
before or if I I'm diving like um is it
host it's interesting and I'm diving in
and I'm you know crawling it and I'm you
know messing around with burp and I find
something interesting on that I'm like
oh hey I need to look at this I have all
the excuse me I have all the data
historically stored now I can then now
that identified as a question that needs
to be asked let me go answer that
question with the data that they put
in wow man I the the the breath of it
all is is a little overwhelming to me as
somebody who doesn't really do data
science on all this so like then you
know you you get this does that make
sense because I want to make sure does
that does that make sense does that make
sense because I want to make sure that
that point gets through no it it does so
you know you're looking at a specific
Coast you're saying okay I'm waiting
things like like crawling versus uh you
know hitting various paths I'm hitting
I'm waiting s probably um status codes
and and waiting um you know all these
different attributes of the domain
method used you know get get post put
whatever um and then you know you're
looking at the interesting things from
there um that that all makes sense and
then you find something interesting you
know through manually looking through it
at the end of the day you've actually
got to do the hacking right you got to
read and you got to put together the
attack Vector in your brain um and then
you know you know there's this and
you're looking at all this in the log
file um and so you know then you go back
to ask the data or a question about XYZ
thing and and I guess I imagine this
doesn't take a normal shape right and
this is the sort of the thing that's a
little bit hard for me to wrap my head
around um but you know you you've got
some something like hey uh where do I
see 403s or something like that should I
pay attention to 403s on the specific
endpoint how I mean are you just running
a GP across all of your you know 100
terabytes of files to try to get data on
that question or or what kind of common
forms does this ask the data a question
take sure so I was using like a
standpoint of i' like with a Swagger
that has a variable like it's of 200 and
without the variable I'm not getting
anything I'm like okay that's something
right that is a something I need to be
aware of all right one let me go back
and see if I've ever seen a variable on
a Swagger before and and if I have
what's the frequency of it okay I
haven't okay what if now I then create a
test fuzz that does nothing but fuzz for
um different
variables right values and see if I can
get hit on all those right I've learned
this I've learned that this is now
a new way to extract data how can that I
apply it to all the data that I have
that's very relevant right how do I so
now now then I'm okay extract all the
the whatever Swagger do Json and then
okay I'm going to put together and craft
a specific test that I can measure and
say okay I'm going to put in 50,000
variable names and run this through am I
getting hits oh dang it hit on two okay
it might not be a vulnerability but now
in my head I'm like okay
I need to be aware of this and I need to
be able to then um update my processes
to at least take it into consideration
and then if it's a new the new segment
in okay now I'm starting to measure that
okay how much time am I spending on this
what's my hit rate for this new test
that I've created that is about this one
specific
thing wow okay it's you've said all of
that in different parts now the picture
is getting much clearer so so you're at
you're you're saying okay I've got
variables on the Swagger file I'm going
to scan across all these things to see
where have I ever seen variables on a
Swagger file before and and you're
updating your process to maybe even wait
that higher in the future and say okay
you know if I've got if I've got
something like a Swagger file and then
that's X XYZ waiting uh rating and then
if it has variables oh that's a little
bit more interesting because I'm I'm
getting more deep it also tells you how
complete of assessment you're you're
doing right and so leave your existing
leave your existing uh program going
don't modify it and keep it going it's
all about testing right you're all about
trying to test and find new winners so
you're put together a hypothetical test
you're saying okay let's see if I do
this right and I started with you know
10,000 uh 10,000 different variable
names in my test I only got a hit on you
know five and it was always group one
group two group three group four okay
well that may be an industry standard
it's just group so all I need to do is
those 10 names and put it into the into
the uh into the process and now I got
coverage right I got a process that
takes one second to run and you know
it's going to find incrementally more
than I had did the day
before wow that's pretty lit dude and
and and I think reintegrating all of
that too is really is really uh it's a
challenge from a programming perspective
and one of the things I didn't love
about being an automist back in the day
was this uh you know this concept of I'm
spending so much time programming and it
results in cool bugs uh but I I like to
spend more time you know staring at
other people's code and wondering how to
break it than writing my own crappy code
that's gonna break right right right it
a headache it's a headache and whatever
yeah and most of know a lot I would say
actually this month majority of my time
has been trying to Tinker around and get
my server that one of one of my servers
that broke back up and running right and
that's a pain but whenever it does run
it right I sit down and in a four hours
pull out eight bugs okay great so now if
I can do that every single day but I
just got to get it back and thank
goodness for AI because oh my gosh I
mean the the for me to sit down and code
has a pain but now with AI shoot just I
need this this and this thank you very
much copy paste and that that's amazing
and I want to hear about so obviously
you're using it from a coding
perspective um and I I hate to even ask
this question because we normally try to
stay away from like what programming
language are you using you know you know
sort of questions but I mean what what
are you what are you doing with all this
cuz this is I mean if you're doing all
this in like bash then it's going to be
insane to maintain it is is B I mean it
is all in bash but it's all like um
you're a beast man I don't understand
how you do this so it's it's workflow
type of thing right and in and in bash
and you know I just basically you know
if then okay did the pass this step if
then it's if then steps all the way
through right something come out okay
then then then then simple simple simple
you only focus on one small segment each
time right you've got it yeah
compartmentalized that makes heart and
if somebody would look at my code and
like you are nuts you're not a program
I'm like you're absolutely right I'm not
a program but it works and this is how
I've got it done right I was able to do
it it goes so um but yeah
so bash is a very simple scripting
language and that's very easy for me to
understand if I get into some type of
object oriented I'm going be just lost
um it's just not wow dude that's
legendary they they and I think it
probably really speaks to the
organization of the system as well um
you know having it compartmentalized out
to different pieces um so that that's
really cool I want to go towards the um
the uh working backwards from aone and
learning how to do that and then uh but
before that I want to talk about Source
uh your data sources so you mentioned
before you know you're hitting you've
got these various curated lists that
you've got you mentioned a crawler you
mentioned um security Trails any other
data sources you want to kind of shout
out and share with the people yeah um so
you know whenever you're talking about
paid sources security Trail seems to be
um top spot um I think that I do um yeah
maybe I'm just going off when we we
start taking a look at all the different
sources you can get from you know Zumi
to showan to um binary Edge right I've
I've tested them all and I've integrated
them all um some I've
cut um but yeah so I'm I'm doing all
that so those are those are the data
sets some are free some are not
right so let's go back to so we talking
about this let's talk about you know how
to incorporate scope management this
whole data management or data science
thing right I prioritize um so I have a
scope management um Tool uh which which
is basically flat file that has um
program subdomain or cdir blah blah blah
whatever the target type what Target is
um is it end scope what's the platform
what processes I need to include or not
okay if Recons one of those those uh
processes or for pulling data I can
assign it a value of one through
whatever and one is daily or multiple
times a day two is you know I can stage
it so I'm using data science also to
tell me but the frequency in which I
should pull from these locations so then
I'm not wasting money
on I know it's Overkill time but that's
crazy it is a little over I'm not GNA
lie but it's very efficient it is man it
is and querying an API all the time is
gonna cost up cost a ton especially if
you're going for these paid data sources
yeah so I mean you know between data and
servers you know I'm pushing close to5
00 a month right that's a mortgage
payment something wow I was going to ask
that yeah $1,500 a month I mean and and
that doesn't you know a lot of people
would wins at that I know friends that
are in this community that are like ah
$10 a month for a server I'm like come
on but um having this whole access to
this whole data service is is mass
advantageous yeah exactly exactly and
and the other thing with this too from
the automation side is like we've been
talking with people on the podcast
lately about the sort of trade-off of
the we've seen over the past couple
years of less people focusing on recon
and more people focusing on sort of uh
diving deep and knowing the application
not that those are mutually exclusive
but the one thing that I miss about uh
automation stuff is like and I think the
to be honest for me the money sort of
evened out either way but the the one
thing that I miss about the automation
is like ah I'm gonna you know like you
mentioned wake up in the morning get my
cup of coffee sit down and then it's
it's all doing it and if I go to the
Golf Course then it's still working for
me and I don't have to stress like oh
I'm not looking for bugs right now
exactly you know so I do think while
there is stressors of like keeping your
servers up keeping your code maintained
there's a lot of relief that comes as
well from knowing that something's
constantly working something efficient
something that you've built is
constantly working in your favor so
that's definitely something to be
considered for the people that are
looking to have a little bit more of a
relaxed lifestyle kind of like you
mentioned of like pre-retirement sort of
Vibes um that could definitely be a
great solution so yeah if I put a little
commentary to that is that uh I will say
this like whenever I was going crazy
deep dive and doing the things that I
was doing that was so much that was
rewarded so much more right that now
yeah I lost years of my life doing it so
it was a price that I'm sure you did um
but um hands down that was that was much
much much more profitable and and I've
decided to go this way cuz I needed to
reinvent my relationship with bug Bounty
I needed to chill out I needed to get to
another stage of life so I've gone this
automation is Route uh identifies proper
it's not going to find bugs per se it's
going to find me opportunities to find
bugs um and to the point of that um and
you may have a little bit of this just
is that I love create right I love
creating things and hacking is
destroying automation is creating a lot
of is kind of hey I want to build
something and I have hacking is
destroying yeah it is destroy because
because here's the thing right you find
you find a bug you submit it what
residual value does it have it's done
it's gone I've there's nothing there's
nothing else that like will there's no
more return it's not like an annuity and
then like you know every year you're
going to get paid in additional
incremental value of it no it's done so
um you know investing into something
that helps you out and you know I don't
know maybe it's just make the just to
make me feel good I don't know but I
enjoy obviously I'm nuts about this data
stuff
so yeah that's that's very clear not
gonna lie
John that's that's awesome um great so
we covered we covered the um we covered
the the data sources a little bit you
know clearly you're not shying away from
paying for data sources you're clearly
trying to get a lot of coverage
you know pulling from lots of different
places and then sort of determining what
is the best frequency um to do with that
uh and then so bringing it back around
to the how do we how do we identify the
source for our our vulnerability um and
can can you tell me a bit bit about that
system so you you know you you've let's
say you've just found a vulnerability
how are you working back and and letting
that inform what automation stuff you'll
do in the future yeah okay so I get a
vulnerability I subit all
right uh first thing first thing is it a
duplicate or is it is it
new it's a new one it's a new one I like
this though this is good right because
it's a duplicate I'm like [__] why was
I'm not the first right right so it's
it's a new one okay I go through right
so I trace Trace through I see okay how
my content Discovery worked what did it
find whenever I compared to what did I
do to to actually discover the bug right
so it may have alerted me that hey
there's you need to look at this and
then I dive into it and I'm like oh I'm
putting this piece with this piece and
then fully formulating what the bug is
and then ask okay is that something that
could be added or was this just
something that I just need to make sure
that I test whenever I you know this is
something that was a
one-off so that's feedback there then go
back and I say
okay uh when did it enter my content and
how long
after how long did it take from
Discovery and resolution to it to get to
content so I'm taking a look at the time
differential like was my Q too long was
my queue you know it took five hours or
like or do I need to spin up another
server to clear out that queue up right
so I'm looking at the
time um then I'm looking all the way
back and saying okay um what was my data
source right um and that's going to be
like security Trails showan you know C
ranges even and I've got bbot and amass
running on their separate servers right
they're doing their own thing um I'm not
doing the brute forcing right now
because I just got so much whenever I do
run I got so many targets coming in
until it works I just don't have I'm
choking um yeah yeah um so uh so then
you I Trac back through and all the way
back okay it came from security Tri okay
whenever whenever it was what time of
day did I find it did I find it in the
morning did I find it midday did I find
it in afternoon did it resolve the first
time did it like sometimes I I find that
I get a file and it takes it's not till
the second day before it resolves and
gets to my system like okay what
happened there was that an operational
issue was it down right um so I'm trying
to time crunch down uh and find the
areas that okay where are the gaps
because I don't want to be
second and um so do you have like a
specific timeline that you want to see
there like I want to see okay it made it
through my whole pipeline in one day and
I found the vul and that's that's the
the happy path is that I mean yeah what
kind of metrics do you have for that so
so basically my goal is within 18 hours
of discovery
that it's in it's in my
output that's great man that that's
awesome top of your head and that varies
because that's on that's on a Monday a
Saturday and Sunday are going to be
completely different because your number
of targets going to be different and and
and holidays holiday weeks they're
different so all those things taken like
you can now I I look for those things
because when we were doing advertising I
we had to you know know that viewing
habits are going to be different on on
the weekends or or on a uh you know a
holiday right but same thing with work
productivity and releasing new assets
it's the same thing you your your de
teams
are they're going to adjust schedules
based upon the upcoming holidays so you
know absolutely you know the upcoming
you know weekly into a holiday it's
going to be
lightweight and not to be not weekends
same thing you're gonna see less stuff
come up so yeah that that that makes
sense so so just to summarize that
because all of these processes get get
pretty intense you're you you found your
vulnerability it's new you're going back
you're looking at how long it take to go
through your pipeline to get to the
point where it's like hey uh John this
is something you should look at you know
that sort of thing you're trying to
figure out what's happening there and
then are you do you have data on like
hey you know 90% of my vulnerabilities
are coming from you know uh SI or Si
cidr scans on this target like maybe
that's something I should overl you know
spend more time looking into do you have
you done that sort of thing before is
that something do that one off I mean
yeah I do one off I mean it's not like I
got a you know 100 bugs that I'm like
all of a sudden looking through and and
find it but yeah I do see like I mean I
like the indicators of like hey what's
my hit rate for a cidr what Ian how many
how many in
Target how many IPS do I scan is it
really can I prioritize
accordingly do you so I guess in order
to do that you you'd have to log all of
that as well and say okay yeah you know
is there some thing you have that says
okay I found a vulnerability on this
endpoint and it's associated with this
asset and it's associated with this path
and this data source and this sort of
thing so do you have like a like a
database or a file that's full of that
information uh no I should you think I
would I don't have that I mean um
because usually I do it a oneoff when
you talk about a manual thing that's
what I'm going to manually go through
right I I know the indicators
right I I I'm more
I'm to be
completely um managing end yes you would
have that but I I don't think we're I'm
at I think that even goes that's one
level you identify a level before you
found I found the the bottom I found the
endless uh the bottom of the data
science seek that's very cool man
there's there's so many there's so many
possibilities you can do with all that
data too so then taking that extra and
correlating like okay here's the
vulnerability what's the recipe for this
vulnerability well it's an API grouped
uh um you know uh subdomain uh on a on a
you know showd Dan Source domain uh with
a path that
has a word from the you know URL or from
the domain name or something like that
you know even something like that would
be able to just be like oh man that'd be
mindboggling to see all of the the data
you could pull out of there I love that
um so I think you you covered it a
little bit um in we talked about it
briefly in the past but um I think this
is a good transition into the the the um
digital marketing Arena because I've got
some questions about that as well um how
do you apply conversion funnels that the
conversion funnel that you mentioned
before to this this book bounding thing
is that the thing you just described
before or is that something different no
it is it's kind of so in digital
marketing and direct response Marketing
in in a lot of operations there's
measurement that's called a conversion
funnel basically you have X number
coming in and you're you're whittling
down to a certain endpoint so in bug
Bounty right you start with your total
Targets in and you're going to do some
filtering along the way and you're going
to do some processing and then at the
end you're hope that what comes out at
the end is going to be what you're
highly focused on or what you want to to
gain right so in conversion funnels we
used to think about how many how many uh
Impressions do we get how many how many
clicks did it lead to how many form
fields did it lead out to how many
customers did it lead to we monetize
what and then you go through and you
plug all those convered funnels all over
the place and be able to say okay this
is working this is not right same thing
here so in in bug bount's like all my
Assets in right and then they go through
did it resolve did it you know did they
you know eventually did I get to a bug
right and you're looking at all the
different sources so okay you know this
particular
Source um is always the one that find
you know if I'm finding something it's
always security Trails okay well that
tells me something right um that
security Trail funnel is important or
you know if it's a cidr scan okay which
cloud is it coming from which you know
is there a certain um you know region
that's
more more valuable than others um things
of that nature so you got conversion
funnels all over the place and you're
filtering it down
wow that Mak sense that's awesome man so
so yeah that that's a that's a technique
that's borrowed from marketing from the
digital marketing world and then we're
applying this to Assets in the scenario
rather than users in a in a conversion
funel in a traditional sales conversion
funnel and say okay where along this
funnel all right the user comes in they
can land on the website did they fill
out the form no okay so there's some
sort of falloff between the user landing
on the site and then filling out the
form and then you know in our scenario
there's an ass can I use on that group
right do I need to change the color to
the button to be red or purple or green
right like that's where marketing goes
into marketing man great and in this
scenario it's yeah go ahead oh marketing
is is another name for hacking I mean
instead of hacking I mean it relates
hacking relates to computers marketing
relates to people right you're hacking
people yeah um wow yeah go watch go
watch social dilemma uh and then put
your mindset on of like okay
hacking people get people to change
their mind without them knowing have you
seen that movie yet that I I have not
seen it yet that that seems fascinating
so I'm definitely gonna I'm gonna have
to check that out after this um all
right let let me let me get to we have
so many things in this in this document
here that I I need to pick your brain on
um so I guess we'll we'll switch over
now towards the digital marketing area
um and and we've sort of talked about
you know we talked about the content uh
the concept of conversion funnels you
know with people coming in versus assets
coming in and that sort of thing um I'm
wondering I if there's any tips that you
have as a as clearly an industry expert
on digital marketing and that sort of
thing what kind of things do people need
to know when they're looking at a
digital marketing platform from an
attacker perspective because there's a
lot of um L lingo uh marketing concepts
that sort of thing um what data is
important what data is not important um
the people need to understand for them
to be able to have that sort of uh
subject matter expert uh uh approach to
attacking a marketing platform so can
you give us like I know it's a lot
because I know I'm asking you to just
like condense your whole you know work
history and and expertise in digital
marketing into a thing but what kind of
things do we need to know where we're
going to get the most value out of it so
the things you need to know uh is like
with hacking any Target right you need
to know the industries ins and outs the
operations you need to know the
terminology you need to know what's um
what's important to the users what's
important to the business right you need
to understand the ecosystem on how that
works now whenever you get into there
right then you can start looking for
things that are of high value uh that
might be disguised um and um I guess
before I get to that point I would like
to make make say is that with every ad
platform there is tons and tons and tons
of documentation there's a lot of
functionality from the point of at you
know content creation to delivery to
bidding to the result sets and there's a
lot that goes on into that so knowing
all that there's there's
are functionality to to take a look at
now by being a by being somebody that
has a knowledge of hey I was once a
digital Advertiser I know what's
important to me right and I I kind of I
I subject matter expert systems design
know how things should work type thing
you combine those two you take a step up
and you start taking a look at these
platforms right and you you can kind of
see some some areas that uh that
um data shouldn't be
at yeah high that that that that makes
sense sense so I guess without you you
know we uh we walk the line here on
critical thinking quite often of like
give us your secret sauce and tell us
about all of these critical
vulnerabilities you found on all of
these companies that we don't sometime
sometimes we don't explicitly name
sometimes we do explicitly name you know
but a lot of times people know what
we're talking about um so I guess with
that with
that line in mind there um what what
kind of data in those sort of
environments should people be looking to
leak or what kind of data is important
in that in those sort of applications
yes so all the ads are getting published
anyway right you know that's one thing
that I've struggled with obviously
you've got personal information of like
the people you know that are have
accounts on the platforms but like it's
a highly public sort of concept and
somehow you've been able to extract a
ton of money from these these you know
platforms so what data are you getting
so as a consumer yeah it's a very public
thing right you're just being served as
but so as an Advertiser right you're in
direct competition with every other
Advertiser right that real estate space
comes at a price and you're trying to
get the best real estate Pace uh space
Tois price right and it's typically done
through blind auction there's some
public auctions out there now the blind
what is a blind auction auction sorry
that's my sudden accent auction
Au T but what is a blind auction versus
a not blind auction so blind auction is
whenever you're bidding on keywords
right you're saying I'm willing to spend
$437 Sense on this keyword it's a
whatever phrase match blah blah blah for
this demographic and Y yada y right now
that's my bit now if I'm a dollar
over Advertiser B I'm paying way too
much right there's a lot of efficiency
or the inefficiency is very profitable
for these
companies and
and right because you're in competition
you're going to be like okay what is if
I'm Toyota I'm like what's Ford doing
like how are what what's what's their
strategy how much are they spend how
much are they paying in the blind option
what are they doing option I'm saying
option auction
yeah all right so so there's a lot of
there's a lot of data goes around that
is highly sensitive whenever is viewed
from the standpoint of a customer are an
advertiser's
kpi interesting so in those scenarios
you're kind of wanting to pull data on
how much people are paying for
advertising and how much money they're
putting into specific keywords or
specific phrases or specific ads within
their that environment because and maybe
the ad content you know I guess the ad
content is important because you have to
be able to know the keyword but the ad
content is going to get shown to the
user anyway what you're mostly looking
to do is figure out how efficiently
their ads are working and and what their
spend is on those specific things so you
can butt right up to that a little bit
right yeah now now I would say say this
caveat right now if you got to Yahoo now
I'm looking there you will find costs
per you know bid or you know and that's
because the the section that's leaking
that information right now is a public
auction it's p so save everybody the
pain and Agony going oh I found right
now so be careful on that okay but there
there there were times whenever it's a
private a a blind auction and you're
able to strip maybe a find um you find
some kpi data that shouldn't be in there
and um whenever it is uh an issue that
is
um I guess persistant in the overall
design of all your ad display
operations you then have a bug that gets
rolled out
everywhere I see I see okay that that
makes that makes a lot a lot of sense
and I imagine also maybe tell me if I'm
on based or off based with I've done a
little bit of digital marketing myself
that being able to tell the contents of
an ad before that ad runs would that be
would that be something that you know
has high impact to a marketer say like
okay you know Ford is running an ad that
says you know Toyota is break down more
than you know Fords or something I I
don't know you know something like that
having that information in advance would
that be valuable to Toyota or is that
mostly just ah this is going to be
public information anyway it doesn't
really quite
matter you know what I mean you can make
the case because let's say I'm GNA put a
blitz campaign on for the holidays right
I don't want my competition to know what
my marketing message is uh you this is
part of my strategy right I don't know
they shouldn't know anything that I'm
doing uh and any um any hint that
destroys the efficiency of my so yeah
I'd be mad as hell if that leak as an
Advertiser yeah so interesting yeah
think I've got some ad ad platforms that
I I put in the dock that I'm not going
to mention explicitly but uh that I I've
got some stuff on that I need to go back
and revisit I think after this
conversation and maybe I'll I'll hook
you in there there is I mean it when you
talking about adver is a Cutthroat type
of situation I mean there's a there's
there's a lot of uh like spyfu I
remember using I mean you're you're
trying to do anything and everything to
find out what your competitor's keywords
are what they're doing what ads what
their performance was we used all kind
of data aggregators to be able to they
were basically crawling and
screenshotting and doing all that kind
of stuff and providing reports so it's
it's uh it's a yeah it's a competitive
world and so if you can find like that
yeah no um and then I would definitely
spin it up as like no you're you're Brad
about it your industry you make money
from ad sales right and your core Money
Maker is the thing that is uh at risk no
hi definitely that's Ben
yeah I'd love to see you I need to just
invite you in to negotiate for me your
bread and butter your bread and butter
is on the line here no hi
hi no no no that's yeah hi end of story
that's great man so one of the things
one of the things that's a part of your
um sort of hacker signature uh uh that
that I remember you from in the Live
Hack events is this whole con con
concept of a MOAB a mother of all bugs
um that I've heard you talk about and
there was a lot of chatter going around
in the live hacking event scene when you
were crushing it about um you know John
having some sort of secret you know
weapon uh of a bug Golden Goose you know
Moab whatever you want to call it it um
I'm wondering you know obviously in in
one or two live hacking events you've
had something like that that's just
blown up and just You' found a ton of
vulnerabilities with it um I'm wondering
how how often you find stuff like this
where it's like um very systemic you you
had some some criteria criteria here
that you mentioned interview you said no
no one else knows to look for it it can
be found on different host functionality
endpoint making it C spy resistant and
it's a rating of higher critical
that's what You' kind of defined and and
can you talk to us a little bit about
your experiences with those and how
often you're finding them what you're
doing to find
them so
um the one that we were alluding to
earlier about finding you
know finding it uh you find information
or data that you can distract
information from in a place that it
shouldn't be and it's everywhere that is
a MOAB right that was the fundamental
design issue that was persistent and it
was everywhere right it was across think
about every single place that an
advertisement was
displayed it's that's a big
bug all right so other ones there's no
nothing that's been like a MOAB like
that before it was just one issue and it
was persistent everywhere I've been able
to get into like a system and then be
able to do a string of 30 bugs that's
that's another sure sure sure that that
not quite a mo I had a mini Moab uh um
with doesn't quite it doesn't quite meet
the measurement for a MOAB but it's a
mini Moab so in um in that uh 702 that
that that one um my my first um um life
hacking event I I stumbled upon uh the
yql servers everybody knews what they
were at the time you had you could
interact with them some queries for the
most part you didn't know exactly the
basics well there was probably
I don't know 30 servers I'm just making
that up but I don't know what the exact
number is let's say there was 30 of
those servers right and I found one of
the servers that had an API document it
was the only one that had an API
document and that API document gave me
an
endpoint that then could apply to all 30
of those other or 30 hosts oh man MH
yeah and
that API document led to two mediums for
each
host and
then and
then because the endpoints that it would
then you know continue to to provide
when she fuled out the the complete path
there was other opportunities like ssf
are all over place so then you there was
another couple bugs here and there so
the end end of the day right you had one
API document on one host that gave you
enough information to pull 75 80 bugs I
don't I can't remember how was but it
was dude right it rolled out so it was
something that applied to everything um
yeah right time right place um wow
freaking freaking Yahoo man like they
Rock for pay for paying that sort of
thing and and also for having those sort
of
phones I
guess in those sort of scenarios I'm
wondering do you do you automate the
report because it it's like that's like
75 reports you got to write that that's
going to take days just to write the
report yeah simplify copy paste I mean
it was simple I mean that was for the I
mean it was copy paste copy paste and
then I could and refer to report blah
blah blah so it was simple right right
right sure but as far as you know like
autom like that was before um that was
before nuclei right and it was before
FFF um and so I would I had uh in map
and i' i' create an NSC file um and then
it would do my vulnerability John are
you kidding me yeah yeah so that was my
that was my nucle scanner yeah and I
dumped it out and
uh so dude that's like that's like a
really old way of doing it
yeah but I mean I didn't know it would
any better I mean I maybe there were
tools available I like I really
didn't but yeah I was like somehow I
jumped onto the the NC map and but that
was 2016 right there's a lot more
efficient way to do it today that's nuts
man I I just I I love how we all just
got trounced by Uh custom and math
script in that scenario that's that
makes me feel great thank you for that
John but no no no honestly it was really
you found and so yeah you could so yeah
the results of that um the results of
that life packing event
um definitely overqualified me I because
you see the one end point that led to
that then there was this other little
marketing or not sorry not marketing but
uh was a weird metrics panel I've never
seen before it was at one analytics or
metric panel yeah yeah it was it was
weird and I've never seen it before or
after uh and it was for hot minutes
everywhere that's so that's was another
15 20 bugs and then you know layer in a
couple of virtual hosts and you're done
and bang I look like a
rockstar yeah you can you can say that
again dude that that was that was crazy
so I guess so in that scenario yql
server hitting finding an API endpoint
on one of them that or an API
documentation on one of them that just
applied to all of them and just sort of
mass apply the principle kind of like
what you've talked about and then also
being able to identify this metrics
panel that you can spray across all of
them I think I think it's clear you know
your methodology is very um uh I guess
distribution oriented as well you know
hey I'm going to take this thing what
can I apply what else can I apply this
to um and do you have any
specific tips for how to avoid dupes in
this scenario because I feel like Yahoo
is a great program for this um you know
they pay them out each one but some
programs would say ah okay you know the
you know whatever metrics panel we're
gonna we're gonna um we're gonna say
that's this is like a systemic problem
dup it all back to one have you have you
had those and how does that how do you
avoid those scenarios normally you I
can't avoid them
um
uh yeah so each program has its own
personality that's what you have to
understand right and personality is
defined by the management team of that
bug Bounty program some are going to be
hey that's a unique change and um we'll
reward you accordingly so you can have
some that are much more favorable for
the researchers than others and others
are very protective of the business
they're like no that's it's the same
issue it just app
differently yeah I've I've had this I've
had those I've had the situations on the
end it's a gut punch it's an absolute
gut punch
um and uh yeah you got to be thi thick
skinned about it um but yeah I don't
have any way to unless unless you can
kind of prove um prove specifically that
it's Unique effect on each um yeah I can
go into some details on some on uh on a
on a particular experience that I had it
was really rough and you know it's it's
been four years and and I I still still
have a little burn on it and I'm a thick
skinned guy right it doesn't get it but
that one yeah and it was the same thing
right it was like nope it's just this
one fix I'm
like you think so but I can't argue
against you youve you you you've
mentioned you know a burnout that
occurred and You' mentioned sort of the
the ups and downs of of bug Bounty like
you're just talking about right now um I
guess as a more seasoned Hunter that's
been doing this for years what do you
think what are some things you do to Pro
protect yourself nowadays from one
burnout and two uh disappointment
because my wife always says to me I
always run you know whenever I find a
this is what I do John whenever I find a
vulnerability I'm like oh I found
something and then I get up and I run in
the other room and I say hey Mariah you
know I found this $15,000 vul that does
XYZ and she's like did they pay it and
I'm like no and she's
like it's not a 15 ,000 B is it you got
to temper your expectations Justin you
got to not count your eggs before they
hatch because she's seen me go from you
know way up here to go you know down
when it's like a dupe of a 35k bug like
I had earlier this last year um so do
you have any any uh any advice on that
or do you just ride the
wave you know it's hard not to run into
the other room and do your little Victor
Dance I mean that's that yeah I mean
that you're just bug hunting you there's
a dopamine hit right I mean and it
doesn't necessar I mean sometimes it's
the money sometimes it's just oh my God
I just did this I never thought that but
there's a dopamine hit from that all
right yeah that's like with any drug um
and that's the problem that I got into
right I was chasing the high chasing the
high chasing High chasing high and
that's a that's a wrong way to go and it
definitely earns to burn out um but yeah
it's it's so hard I guess there was a
saying that we always said it's like
that's just business right don't take it
personally it's just business um and
that's what I go back to eases the pain
a little bit but no it's still it's
still rough it's still frustrating that
second place first
loser it's true especially in in you
know dup dupe scenarios and stuff like
that where it's like do you do do you do
D anal do you go
I'm sorry I didn't mean to talk over you
but do you do dup analysis no no yeah I
do I it it hurts a little bit you know
to go back and say like and and it kind
of distracts me a little bit from the
pain of the dupes too you're like all
right why did this get dupes you know
like why why am I getting duped on this
you know and so you go back and you look
and sometimes you can draw a correlation
when you've got monitoring stuff in
place and you can say okay you know I
didn't react to this alert fast enough
especially when it's the stuff that's
real tight you know I duped by like a
couple hours or something but um
you know most of the time for me it's
like okay I spent some time looking at
this specific thing and
somebody you know beat me to it by a
little bit that's how it is that's
that's how the cards lie but then when
there's scenarios where it's like ah
this bug has been open for six months
and it's still not resolved you know
that that's a real hard sell for me to
go back to that program like like I I
and I I tell them that in the report too
I'm like hey guys I know Noti that the
report ID that I'm duped to on this one
is over 6 months old it's a crit why is
this happening you know and and I I'll
specifically request an explanation or
some sort of uh you know response for
that because I feel like that's a little
bit of a a violation of of hacker trust
in that scenario because it's like we
are putting in our time for a
results-based
thing right and we provided you a result
we provided you with a vulnerability and
if you're you can't protect our time
with that by getting these resolved at a
at a at a decent pace then our Roi for
this you know this program goes down
substantially um yeah so that's I mean
that's kind of where I'm at with dupe
analysis I don't know yeah no I to your
point like I always try to you know if I
have some type of question sometimes I
know a dupe like I'm I'm putting in the
report like this 100% this is a dupe um
but sometimes if I don't understand even
if I know it's going to be a dupe I like
how far am I behind I'll ask for the
report ID in 12 hours I'm like see what
happens here
but
yeah um yeah I was trying to I imagine
definitely in the yeah please please ask
more questions I love it when when guest
do that you know especially in the
scenarios when you're in an in an
automation flow you know I I I remember
we talked about it on the episode with
uh with Shan sha yo from um from aset
note you know there was a time where him
and I were just going back and forth and
back and forth and back and forth with
these takeovers and I was like dang it
Sean's beating me yes I'm beating Shawn
yes tanging Sean's video you know it's
just back and forth and uh it's a lot of
fun man it's it's entertaining but man
does its sting when you say ah man Shawn
made $10,000 today from uh something
that I could have done if I had just
written my code a little bit better you
know right
exactly yeah yeah it's it's it's a lot
man um I I'm looking at this document uh
you know we we still have so much that
that we could cover on here um and we've
we've had so much uh so so much good
content so far already um unfortunately
we've got to bring it to a close because
I do have a stop but um John thank you
so much for coming on man is there
anything else you wanna you want to
shout out or you want to discuss in the
last couple minutes here no I just want
to say thank you so much uh for having
me on and um for the content creators in
this in the space has off to you um oh
my gosh I know that's a it's a burden of
love but uh it's so greatly appreciated
and um you know what you guys do is
fantastic fantastic so keep up to good
work and uh be tuning in that's awesome
thank you so much John yeah I I I really
I really do appreciate that it is it is
a lot of it's a it's a lot of work uh
but you get a lot of love out of it too
from people like you and and also you
know you coming on the show and stuff
like that it really it eases it eases
the load because all I've got to do is
sit here and be in you know dump my
brain of like all right how does he do
it you know and uh and then get the
answers so it's a great it's a great
experience for me as
well all righty I think I think with
that we'll close uh once again John Mr
my eyes Mr mayonnaise thanks for coming
on and uh we'll see you on the hacker
one leaderboards sounds great thank you
very
much
peace